Dennou Boukenki
Plan
Webdiver Production Committee
Original Plan
Ishikawa Hiroto
Series Composition
Sekijima Mayori
Character Design
Takahashi Naruyo
Concept Design
Color Scheme
Moriki Yasuhiro
Kawami Takuya
Production Designer
Director of Audiography
Composite Director
Iwase Eiji
Tanaka Hideyuki
Nagaushi Yutaka
Music
Music Producer
Music Collaboration
Hayashi Yuzo
Kumada Kazuo
Television Tokyo Music
Opening Theme
Lyrics
Composer/Arrangement
Takatori Hideaki
Hirama Akihiko
Song
Columbia Japan
Production Collaboration
Animation Production
Animation Producer
AEON (We've)
Kachihide Yuki
Nomura Hiroshi
Director
Okajima Kunitoshi
Producer
Iwata Makiko (TV Tokyo)
Yamazaki Tatsuji
Chief Director
Negishi Hiroshi
Production
사랑하는 할아버지께.
Dear Grandpa.
Teruntuk Kakek.
메리 크리스마스!
Merry Christmas!
Selamat Hari Natal!
저도 친구들도 모두 건강하니까 걱정할 필요 전혀 없어요!
All of us are well; no need to worry!
Aku dan yang lainnya baik-baik saja, jadi jangan khawatir!
그리고 밥 제때제때 잘 먹는 거,
And don't forget while working that
Jangan lupa untuk makan teratur juga.
일에 몰중하다 잊으시면 안 돼요.
you have to eat timely!
Jangan sampai lupa karena terlalu sibuk kerja!
제가 돌아갈 때까지 건강히 계세요!
Then, be well until I get back!
Tetaplah sehat wal afiat hingga aku kembali, ya.
역시 메일이 전달되지 않는구나.
The mail is just not being sent.
Suratnya memang tidak bisa terkirim, ya.
몇 번을 시도해도 마찬가지에용. 데리트로스 게이트를 지키는 데리트로스 아이를 물리치지 않으면 통신은 불가능해용.
It failed ever since you tried to send-pyoko. We wouldn't be able to communicate as long as Deletloss Eye is protecting Deletloss Gate.
Sama saja hasilnya berapa kali dicoba-pyoko. Kita harus mengalahkan Deletloss Eye yang melindungi Deletloss Gate agar bisa berkomunikasi-pyoko.
할아버지...
Grandpa...
Kakek...
류토 님, 또 데리트로스 아이가 메일을 파괴했습니다.
Master Ryuto, Deletloss Eye has destroyed the mail again.
Tuan Ryuto, Deletloss Eye telah menghancurkan sebuah surat lagi.
쓸모없는 짓이군.
Good luck sending your mail.
Usaha yang percuma.
데리트로스 게이트는 탈출 불가능.
Nothing may escape from Deletloss Gate.
Tidak ada yang bisa kabur dari Deletloss Gate.
통신도 마찬가지지.
And nothing may communicate, too.
Bahkan berkomunikasi sekalipun.
마음을 동여매라! 출격 웹나이트
Bind the Spirits!
Go Fight, Webknights
Hubungkan Perasaan! Berangkatlah, Webknights
아오이!
Aoi!
켄토! 모두!
Kento! Everyone!
Kento! Semuanya!
어땠어?
How did it go?
Bagaimana hasilnya?
-그렇구나.
-저런, 메일을 보낼 수 없었다니.
-I see.
-Too bad you couldn't sent the mail.
-Jadi begitu.
-Sayang pesannya tidak bisa terkirim.
할아버지께 우리가 건강하다는 것이라도 알릴 수 있다면 좋을 텐데.
I'd like to let my grandpa know that we're safe and sound at here, for the least.
Padahal aku hanya ingin memberitahu Kakek kalau kita semua baik-baik saja.
역시 류토를 쓰러뜨리지 않으면 안 되나 봐.
That's why we have to take Ryuto down.
Berarti, kita memang harus mengalahkan Ryuto.
그런가 보네.
You can say that again.
Sepertinya begitu.
할아버지...
Grandpa...
Kakek...
역시, 아오이는 얘야!
Whoa, I didn't knew Aoi is still a kiddo!
Ternyata Aoi memang masih anak-anak, ya!
그래! 어려!
Nope! More of a crybaby!
Benar! Cengeng sekali!
뭐라고? 내가 어딜 봐서 얘인데?!
What was that?! I have never cried ever since we came here!
Apa maksudmu?! Tidak pernah sekalipun aku bertingkah seperti bocah!
그러니까, 나, 아빠하고 멀리 떨어져 있어도 전혀 그립지 않은걸?
I define a crybaby as one whoever needs her grandpa, and you're a perfect example!
Habisnya, aku saja sama sekali tidak kangen ayahku walaupun terpisah begini.
나도 당연히!
Of course!
Benar sekali!
가자, 카론!
Let's go, Karon!
Ayo kita pergi, Karon!
정말, 둘 다 섬세함 따위는 없어가지고 원!
Where's their manners?!
Dasar, tidak peka sekali mereka berdua!
어?
Huh?
Eh?
진짜!
Again!
Apa-apaan!
물도 안 긷어놓고 나무도 안 해놓고! 얘들 또 뺀질거린다! 다들 어디서 뭐하는 거야?
Neither of water nor firewood is ready! They keep shirking! What are they doing, anyway?
Airnya belum diambil, kayunya pun belum dikumpulkan! Lagi-lagi mereka bermalas-malasan! Sedang apa sih mereka sebenarnya?!
아오이!
Aoi!
이 나무는 어떨까.
Will this tree work?
Kalau pohon ini, bagaimana?
크기는 딱 적당한 것 같아.
The size is just right.
Menurutku ukurannya pas.
전나무라면 더 좋았을 텐데. 어쨌든, 이걸로 일단 때우자.
It could have been better with a fir tree. Anyway, let's make up with this for now.
Seandainya ada pohon cemara, pasti lebih pas. Ya sudah, kita usahakan dulu dengan yang ini.
좋아, 이 나무 데이터를 보내자!
Great! Let's send the data of this tree!
Oke, kuambil dulu data pohon ini.
다들 저기 있잖아?
Do they really have to take that tree?
Itu, kan, Kento dan yang lain.
카론, 거기에 나무 데이터 보낼게.
Karon, prepare to fetch the tree data.
Karon, aku kirimkan data pohonnya, ya.
데이터 수신뾰꼬!
Data receiving-pyoko!
Menerima data-pyoko!
데이터 수신 완료뾰꼬!
Data receive complete-pyoko!
Data telah diterima-pyoko!
나머지는 알아서 잘 해줘, 카론!
The rest is up to you, Karon!
Kuserahkan selanjutnya padamu, Karon!
뭘 하는 걸까...
What can be they up to...
Apa yang sebenarnya mereka lakukan?
안돼!
Stop!
Berhenti!
자, 잠깐, 멈춰!
Stupid wind, stop blowing!
T-tunggu!
나오키 특제 리조트! 많이 먹어!
Naoki's Special Risotto! Fill your stomach up!
Risotto Spesial Khas Naoki! Makan yang lahap, ya!
나오키의 점심을 제일 먼저 클리어하면 저녁은 아오이야. 그럼...
I wouldn't be able to have Aoi's fantastic dinner if I die while eating Naoki's toxic lunch. Here goes nothing...
Asalkan hidangan Naoki bisa kuhabiskan, nanti malam aku bisa makan hidangan Aoi. Baiklah...
다들 있잖아...
Hey, all...
Eh, semuanya...
아까 나무 뒤에서 뭐 했어?
what did you do behind the tree?
Tadi kalian sedang apa di belakang sekolah?
-어, 봤어?
-응.
-Did you see us?
-Yeah.
-Eh, kamu lihat?
-Iya.
음, 그러니까 그건, 그거 말이지!
Heh, that's... um...
U-um, itu... itu loh!
크리스마스하고 전혀 관계 없어!
It has nothing to do with Christmas!
Tidak ada hubungannya dengan natal sama sekali, kok!
크리스마스?
Christmas?
Natal?
아무것도 아니야, 아오이.
It's nothing, Aoi!
Bukan apa-apa, Aoi!
그건 그란모바일러 기능 체크였지, 켄토?
That was a functionality check for Granmobiler, right, Kento?
Itu hanya pengecekan fungsi di Granmobiler. Iya kan, Kento?
응, 맞아!
O-of course!
Ya, ya, itu benar!
다들 왜 저런대.
Everything's not right.
Aneh sekali rasanya.
아, 오늘 크리스마스구나.
Oh, today is Christmas...
Ah, hari ini natal....
아오이.
Aoi.
데리러 왔어, 아오이.
I'm here for you, Aoi.
Aku datang menjemputmu.
울지 마, 아오이. 아빠도 엄마도 이제 없지만, 지금부터 내가 널 지켜 줄 테니까. 같이 다이버랜드에 가자구나.
Don't cry, Aoi. Your mommy and daddy might not be here, but I am still here for you. Let's go to Diverland together.
Jangan menangis, Aoi. Walaupun kedua orang tuamu tidak ada, mulai sekarang akulah yang akan melindungimu. Ayo kita ke Diverland bersama-sama.
그 때부터 매년 크리스마스는 언제나 할아버지하고 같이 있었어.
From that day, I have always been with my grandpa.
Sejak saat itu, setiap tahun aku selalu merayakan natal dengan Kakek!
자!
Look!
Lihat ini!
할아버지...
Grandpa...
Kakek...
-아오이에게 들키면 안 돼.
-응.
-Don't be noticed.
-I won't.
-Masih belum ketahuan Aoi, kan?
-Iya.
-가자.
-응!
-Let's go.
-Sure!
-Ayo pergi.
-Iya!
매지컬 스테이션에 플러그 잇!
To Magical Station, Plug It!
Menuju Magical Station, Plug It!
카론은 데이터 실체화를 해 줘. 우린 다른 준비를 하자.
Karon, transform the data to a tree. We'll do the rest.
Karon, tolong ubah data pohonnya, ya. Kami akan mempersiapkan yang lain.
-응!
-Sure!
-Great!
Baik!
글라디온, 그건 어떻게 되어 가?
Gladion, how's that going?
Gladion, bagaimana persiapan yang itu?
-잘 되어가고 있어.
-정말? 고마워, 글라디온.
-Pretty well, thank you.
-No, I thank you, Gladion.
-Sepertinya berjalan lancar.
-Benarkah? Terima kasih, Gladion.
있잖아, 다른 웹나이트는?
How's the other Webknights?
Bagaimana dengan Webknights yang lain?
매지컬 스테이션에 있는 건 여덟 명이고, 가륜, 드라그온, 다이탈리온은
There are eight of us in Magical Station. Garyun, Dragwon, and Ditalion are
Ada delapan dari kami di Magical Station selain Garyun, Dragwon dan Ditalion
너희들이 있는 버추얼 다이버랜드를 ~에서 배리어로 지키고 있어.
protecting Virtual Diverland that you are at with the barrier from ~.
yang sedang membuat barier untuk melindung Virtual Diverland, tempat kalian tinggal.
그랬구나...
I didn't knew...
Oh, begitu.
부활한 라이거온하고 페가시온도 다이탈리온하고 함께 있어.
Ligeron and Pegasion are with Ditalion, just to say.
Ligeron dan Pegasion yang telah dihidupkan kembali juga bersama Ditalion.
그렇구나! 모두 돌아와서 다행이야!
I see! Great to know everyone's back!
Wah, iya! Syukurlah semua telah kembali!
여기가 사령실인가.
Pretty small for a control room.
Jadi ini, ruang kendalinya.
-살짝이야, 카이토.
-응.
-A little bit, Kaito.
-Okay.
-Pelan-pelan, Kaito.
-Oke.
좋아, 잘 했어.
Good job.
Kerja yang bagus.
왜, 글라디온?
What's wrong, Gladion?
Ada apa, Gladion?
지금 매지컬 스테이션 안에서 사악한 기운을 느꼈는데.
I just sensed a scent of Evil Aura inside Magical Station.
Aku baru saja merasakan hawa jahat di Magical Station, tapi...
쟈기?
Evil Aura?
Hawa jahat?
근데 누가 침입하면 경보가 울리지 않아?
I thought the alarm is supposed to ring if anyone intrudes!
Tapi, bukankah seharusnya alarm-nya berbunyi kalau ada penyusup?
-응.
-뭐, 그럼 준비를 계속 해야지!
-It is.
-Well, then we'll continue the preparation!
-Benar.
-Daripada memusingkan itu, lebih baik kita lanjutkan persiapannya!
여전히 쓸데없는 짓을 하고 있군, 켄토. 그렇다고 나와의 게임을 잊으면 곤란해.
That's the most useful thing that you did ever since I know you. You deserve to forget about and lose the game against me.
Seperti biasa, kau selalu melakukan hal yang sia-sia saja, Kento. Tapi, bisa gawat kalau kau sampai melupakan permainan denganku.
없어!
Not here!
Tidak ada!
없어!
Not here!
Tidak ada!
얘들 또 뺀질거린다! 물도 장작도 안 하면 밥도 못 하잖아.
They shirked again! I can't prepare for dinner without water and wood!
Mereka bermalas-malasan lagi! Kalau tidak ada air dan kayu, mana bisa mempersiapkan makan!
더 이상 용서할 수 없으니까!
I won't stand this!
Aku tidak akan memaafkan ini!
또 잊어먹은 거 찾아달라니 켄토도 건망증이 걸렸나뾰꼬...
To ask me to get something he forget again, he must've got an amnesia-pyoko...
Duh, seenaknya menyuruhku ambil barang ketinggalan. Kento kasar sekali memperlakukan robot-pyoko...
찾았다뾰꼬!
Here it is-pyoko!
Ini dia-pyoko!
뭐야, 이건?
What's this?
Apa ini?
카론, 이거 어디다 쓸 거야? 괜찮으면 다들 어디 있는지 알려주면 좋겠는데 말이지.
Karon, what's this for? I'd like you to tell me where everybody are.
Karon, ini untuk apa? Aku akan senang kalau kau juga memberitahu di mana yang lain sekarang.
아는 거 없어뾰꼬.
I know nothing-pyoko.
Aku tidak tahu apa-apa-pyoko.
정말 몰라뾰꼬!
I have an amnesia-pyoko!
Serius, aku benar-benar tidak tahu-pyoko!
데려가 줄래? 켄토가 있는 곳으로.
Would you take me to where Kento is?
Kau akan mengantarku ke tempat Kento dan yang lain, kan?
가지 않는 게 낫다고 생각해뾰꼬!
You shouldn't go there-pyoko!
Sebaiknya kau tidak masuk dulu-pyoko!
안돼! 모두 뭘 하면서 뺀질거리는지 알아내야 하니까!
No! I just want to know what are they goofing off with!
Tidak mau! Akan kucari tahu apa yang sedang mereka lakukan hingga tidak melakukan pekerjaannya!
Brought to you by Subdiver
-아오이!
-왜 여기에...
-Aoi!
-We weren't ready...
-Kenapa kau di sini...
이건!
Too late!
Ini!
결국 들켰네!
You found it out!
Yah, ketahuan, deh!
어쩔 수 없지. 더 이상 숨길 수가 없어.
Too bad. We can't hide from you any more.
Apa boleh buat. Kita tidak bisa menyembunyikannya lagi.
사실은 크리스마스 파티 준비하고 있었어.
We were preparing for Christmas party.
Sebenarnya, kami sedang mempersiapkan untuk pesta natal.
크리스마스 파티?
Christmas party?
Pesta natal?
아오이, 요즘 쓸쓸해 보여서 말이야. 케이크만 다 되면 그 때 부르려고 했는데!
Aoi, you looked lonely recently. We were planning to call you when the cake is ready!
Soalnya akhir-akhir ini Aoi terlihat sedih, jadi kami berencana melakukan hal yang menyenangkan dengan kue!
-날 위해서?
-당연하지.
-For me?
-Of course.
-Demi aku?
-Tentu saja.
이상한 소리 하긴 했어도 사실 우리도 그리웠어.
We're sorry for what we said before. Actually, we were lonely too.
Aku tidak tahu bagaimana harus mengatakannya, tapi sebenarnya kami juga kangen.
아오이에게 쓸쓸한 얼굴은 안 어울려.
A lonely face doesn't fit Aoi.
Aoi tidak cocok bermuka murung terus.
파티로 아오이가 조금이라도 기뻐질 수 있다면,
If Aoi can be happy with the party,
Kalau pesta ini dapat menghapus kesedihan Aoi walaupun sedikit saja,
우리 웹나이트들도 행복할 거야.
We Webknights will also be happy.
kami para Webknights akan senang juga.
글라디온... 모두!
Gladion... you all!
Gladion... semuanya!
게다가 아오이에게 크리스마스는 특별한 날이잖아.
Moreover, Christmas is a special day for you, Aoi.
Lagipula, bagi Aoi, natal adalah hari yang spesial, kan?
켄토, 모두, 고마워!
Kento. Everyone, thank you!
Kento, semuanya, terima kasih!
계획보다는 조금 이르지만, 크리스마스 파티 시작이야!
A bit earlier than planned, but anyway, Christmas party starts now!
Walaupun lebih cepat dari rencana, mari kita mulai pestanya!
응!
Great!
Iya!
메리 크리스마스!
Merry christmas!
Selamat hari natal!
크리스마스 선물? 나한테?
Christmas present? For me?
Kado natal untukku?
응. 사령실에서 봐봐.
That's right. Your first class seat is at the control room.
Iya. Lihatlah di ruang kendali.
웹다이브! 글라디온!
Webdive! Gladion!
긴급 발진 대기중.
Emergency dispatch, standby.
Siap untuk diluncurkan.
글라디온, 출동.
Gladion, shoot.
웹체인지! 글라디온, 파이터 모드!
Webchange! Gladion, Fighter Mode!
왜 다 발진한 거야?
Why did everybody went out?
Kenapa semuanya berangkat?
이거야.
This.
Karena ini.
파티의 메인 이벤트는 이 통신 프로그램의 발사야.
The main event of this party is shooting this communication program.
Acara utama dari pesta ini adalah peluncuran program komunikasi ini.
통신 프로그램? 설마!
Communication program? That means!
Program komunikasi? Berarti!
응, 성공하면 반드시 아리스가와 박사님하고 대화할 수 있을 거야!
Yeah, you'll be able to have a conversation with Prof. Arisugawa if we succeed!
Iya. Kalau berhasil, kau pasti bisa berbicara dengan Prof. Arisugawa juga!
모두 제 위치로!
Everyone, to your positions!
Semuanya, bersiap pada posisi!
-가자!
-좋아!    -좋아!
-Let's go!
-Ready!        -Ready!
-Ayo mulai!
-Siap!        -Siap!
데리트로스 게이트에서 우리가 활동할 수 있는 시간은 제한되어 있어.
We cannot move in Deletloss Gate for long.
Di dalam Deletloss Gate, durasi aktivitas kita terbatas.
그 짧은 순간에 필살기로 데리트로스 아이를 잠시 막고 통신 프로그램을 데리트로스 게이트에서 바깥으로 보내야 해.
We'll stop Deletloss Eye for a short moment with all our final attacks, and then send the communication program to outside of Deletloss Gate.
Dalam waktu yang singkat itu, kita akan kalahkan Deletloss Eye dengan jurus andalan kita, dan melemparkan program komunikasinya dari sini.
다가와!
Incoming!
Dia datang!
우리부터 공격하겠어! 개틀링 버스터!
We'll attack first! Gatling Buster!
Kami akan menyerang duluan! Gatling Buster!
아쿠아 토네이도!
Aqua Tornado!
호밍 샷!
Homing Shot!
다만, 통신은 데리트로스 게이트가 복구되기까지의 짧은 시간동안만 가능해.
Keep in mind that you can communicate for only a short time until Deletloss Gate recovers itself.
Tapi, kau hanya bisa berkomunikasi sebentar hingga Deletloss Gate selesai menyembuhkan diri.
다음은 우리 차례죠!
It's our turn now!
Selanjutnya giliran kami!
히트 웨이브!
Heat Wave!
어쩌면 너희들 중 한 명밖에 이야기하지 못할지도 몰라.
It's quite a possibility that only one of you get to talk.
Mungkin hanya kamu sendiri yang bisa berbicara saat itu.
스파이럴 커터!
Spiral Cutter!
자이언트 드릴!
Giant Drill!
혼자...
Only one...
Hanya aku...
일렉트릭 랜서!
Electric Lancer!
미라지 소드!
Mirage Sword!
순조로워뾰꼬. 다음엔 데리트로스 링 바깥으로 통신 프로그램을 발사할 거야뾰꼬.
It's going well-pyoko. Next, we'll dispatch the communication program to outside of Deletloss Ring.
Berjalan lancar-pyoko. Selanjutnya, kita tembakkan program komunikasinya ke luar Deletloss Ring.
켄토! 글라디온!
Kento! Gladion!
-와이버리온!
-간다!
-Wyverion!
-Got it!
-Siap!
글라디온, 빅토리 모드!
Gladion, Victory Mode!
웹체인지! 와이버리온, 윙 모드!
Webchange! Wyverion, Wing Mode!
빅토리 글라디온!
Victory Gladion!
가자!
Let's go!
Ayo kita lakukan ini!
빅토리 참!
Victory Slash!
그렇게는 안 되지, 켄토.
In your dreams, Kento.
Tidak akan kubiarkan, Kento.
뭐야?!
What the?!
Apa?!
데리트로스 몬스터?
Deletloss Monster?
말했지? 통신 따윈 용서할 수 없다고.
Told you. No communication allowed.
Sudah kubilang. Takkan kuizinkan komunikasi apapun.
비켜, 류토!
Get lost, Ryuto!
Minggir, Ryuto!
어떻게든 하고 싶으면 이 게라크를 쓰러뜨리면 된다.
If you really want to do that, just take this Geraku down.
Kalau kau memaksa, coba saja kalahkan Geraku ini.
상황이 좋지 않아뾰꼬. 우물쭈물대다가는 데리트로스 링이 풀려나버려뾰꼬.
It's not good-pyoko. Deletloss Ring is going to set loose if we can't make it in time.
Gawat-pyoko. Kalau kita terlalu lama, Deletloss Ring akan semakin menjauh-pyoko.
켄토.
Kento.
자, 어쩔래, 켄토?
Try something, Kento.
Nah, bagaimana, Kento?
이대로 끝나 물러서게 될 수는 없다!
We will not withdraw our plan like this!
Tidak akan kubiarkan berakhir seperti ini!
그란발칸!
Granvulcan!
아직이다. 어쩔 속셈이냐.
Nope. Your plan is invalid.
Apa maksudmu?!
이럴 속셈이다!
Invalid your logic!
Ini maksudku!
빅토리 참!
Victory Slash!
내가 웹다이브하지 않으면 저렇게 간단히 쓰러져 버리는군.
My Christmas present for you kids is that Webmonster without me as an Webdiver.
Tak kusangka akan dikalahkan semudah ini ketika aku tidak Webdive ke dalamnya.
켄토! 시간이 없어! 데리트로스 링이 보일 동안!
Kento! There's no time! Deletloss Ring is up there!
Kento! Tidak ada waktu lagi! Selagi Deletloss Ring masih terlihat!
-그래, 이판사판이야! 가자, 글라디온!
-좋아!
-Right, anything is better than nothing! Go, Gladion!
-Then!
-Baiklah, mari kita coba! Ayo, Gladion!
-Ya!
가자!
Let's go!
Meluncurlah!
됐다!
They did it!
Berhasil!
켄토!
Kento!
통신이 닿아뾰꼬!
The communication is working!
Komunikasinya tersambung-pyoko!
아오이! 박사님하고 이야기해 봐.
Aoi! Talk to your grandpa while you can!
Aoi! Cobalah berbicara dengan Profesor!
어? 근데 혼자밖에...
What about you? Everyone else?
Eh? Tapi, kalau hanya sendiri...
나, 아빠하고 떨어져 있어도 전혀 그립지 않다고!
I'm still not a crybaby. I don't need to talk with them!
Walaupun berpisah dari ayah, aku tidak kangen sama sekali!
않아!
I can't lose!
Sama sekali!
모두!
Everyone!
Semuanya!
여긴 월드 링크 관리국. 들리는가? 여긴 월드 링크...
This is Administration Center. Can you hear me? This is...
Ini adalah Stasiun Pengendali World Link. Bisakah didengar? Ini adalah...
할아버지! 할아버지! 할아버지!
Grandpa! Grandpa! Grandpa!
Kakek! Kakek! Kakek!
아오이! 아오이구나!
Aoi! Is that truly you, Aoi?
Aoi! Apakah itu kamu?
할아버지...
Grandpa...
Kakek...
아오이...
Aoi...
뭔 일이냐, 아오이?
What's the problem, Aoi?
Kenapa, Aoi?
곧 통신이 끊겨버릴 거야뾰꼬.
The communication will be cut soon-pyoko...
Sebentar lagi koneksinya akan terputus-pyoko...
할아버지! 시간이 없어요! 저흰 데리트로스 게이트에 있어요.
Grandpa! There's no time! We are currently in the Deletloss Gate.
Kakek! Aku tidak punya waktu lagi! Kami sedang berada di Deletloss Gate.
그래도 다들 잘 있어요! 우리 반드시 돌아갈 테니까! 그러니까... 그러니까...
But don't worry, we're all well here! We'll definitely go back! So... so...
Tapi Kento dan yang lain baik-baik saja! Kami pasti akan kembali! Lalu... lalu...
그러니까...
so...
Lalu...
할아버지, 메리 크리스마스!
Merry Christmas, Grandpa!
Selamat hari natal, Kakek!
할아버지...
Grandpa...
Kakek...
아오이...
Aoi...
미안하다, 아오이. 우리가 줄 수 있는 선물은 이 정도야.
Apologies, Aoi. This is all we can do.
Maafkan kami, Aoi. Hanya hadiah ini yang bisa kami berikan.
아냐. 이걸로도 충분해. 이렇게 올해도 할아버지하고 크리스마스를 보낼 수 있었으니까.
This is already more than enough. You helped me have a Christmas with my grandpa this year too.
Tidak, kok. Ini sudah cukup, karena tahun ini pun aku bisa merayakan natal dengan Kakek.
모두, 대단한 선물 고마워!
Thanks for the grand gift, everybody!
Semuanya, terima kasih atas kadonya yang indah!
천만의 말씀!
Our pleasure!
Sama-sama!
Screenplay
Maeyamada Ken'ichi
Storyboarding
Staging
Ishiyama Hiroshi
Okajima Kunitoshi
Voice Actor
Yuuki Kento
Gladion
Arisugawa Aoi
Asaba Naoki
Takeuchi Junko
Kobayashi Yumiko
Sugita Tomokazu
Kikuchi Shiho
Kurachi Shou
Kaida Yuki
Voice Actor
Jean J. Jekyll
Nakai Masataka
Yuuki Kaito
Takagi Reiko
Arisugawa Professor
Tobita Nobuo
Ryuto
Yoshino Hiroyuki
Lada
Nakamura Yuuichi
Voice Actor
Jaguaron
Kawashima Tokuyoshi
Phoenixon
Suzumura Ken'ichi
Kerberion
Miyashita Sumio
Orthorion
Suyama Akio
Wyverion
Konishi Katsuyuki
Ending Theme
Lyrics
Oikawa Neko
Composer
Suzuki Kisaburo
Arranger
Kouno Yougo
Singer
Kageyama Hironobu
Insert Song
Lyrics
Composer
Suzuki Kisaburo
Arranger
Kyouda Seiichi
Singer
Columbia Japan
Production Cooperation
Animation Production
AEON (We've)
Subtitle
Subdiver
ファン字幕
サブダイバー
Thank you for watching!
Production
다음 이야기 미리보기
Preview for Next Episode
Episode Selanjutnya
좋아! 모두 오늘도 힘내서 살아남아 보자!
Another day of survival! Do your best to live on!
Baiklah, semua! Hari ini pun, mari bertahan hidup dengan penuh semangat!
언제나하고 다름없는 날을 보내는 것 같지만, 사실은 적이 조용히 움직이고 있었어.
We thought nothing new was happening, but an enemy was moving silently.
Di tengah hari yang seharusnya berjalan seperti biasa, sebuah musuh diam-diam bergerak di balik layar.
내 최대의 약점이 밝혀진다니? 어둠 속을 ~의 정체는, 그리고 류토가 노리는 건..
My biggest vulnerability revealed? What's ~ night? And Ryuto's aim is?
Kekurangan terbesarku terkuak? Lalu, siapa di balik bayangan yang bergeliut, dan apa sasaran Ryuto?
전뇌모험기 웹다이버의 다음 이야기!
Next episode of Dennou Boukenki Webdiver!
Di episode Dennou Boukenki Webdiver selanjutnya!
Thanks for watching! - Subdiver
See you at http://subdiver.soreepeong.com/ !